<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>The Unnamed Blog of Stuff: Posts tagged 'Personal'</title>
  <description>The Unnamed Blog of Stuff: Posts tagged 'Personal'</description>
  <link>http://blog.fortlogic.net/tags/Personal.html</link>
  <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 04:50:12 UT</lastBuildDate>
  <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 04:50:12 UT</pubDate>
  <ttl>1800</ttl>
  <item>
   <title>First Post!</title>
   <link>http://blog.fortlogic.net/blog/2014/06/13/first-post/?utm_source=Personal&amp;utm_medium=RSS</link>
   <guid>urn:http-blog-fortlogic-net:-blog-2014-06-13-first-post</guid>
   <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2014 04:50:12 UT</pubDate>
   <description>&lt;html&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Huzzah! Wewewew! Will you look at that, first post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, I&amp;rsquo;m Matias Eyzaguirre and &lt;span style="font-style: italic"&gt;this&lt;/span&gt; is my blog of stuff. Here you will find lots of
cool things and projects of mine, in addition to ramblings about life, the universe, and everything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I said, I am Matias Eyzaguirre. I am a 23 year old gay male living in Utah. I like math,
programming, science fiction, crochet, and tatting among other things. A problem with trying to
describe myself is that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to prevent it from sounding like a personals ad, so I think I&amp;rsquo;ll
stop here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A blog seems like the sort of thing that someone like me would have, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking of
starting one for a while now. Thinking about it won&amp;rsquo;t do much by itself, so It&amp;rsquo;s time to stop putting
it off and just &lt;span style="font-style: italic"&gt;do&lt;/span&gt; it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m still not really sure what kind of material will go into this blog. It&amp;rsquo;ll probably
end up consisting of posts about math or programming, along with little programming how-tos for
various tasks that I find myself needing to do without any documentation to rely on. And of course
I&amp;rsquo;ll also do write-ups of any mini-projects that I think are interesting, and possible progress
reports for larger projects, who knows?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>